VIVEKA MASSEY

CONTENT WRITER | BLOGGER | CREATIVE WRITER

、 (+91) 8077028856 | ☑ rebekah.251@outlook.com | # https://viveka-portfolio.vercel.app/ | in viveka-massey | Agra, Uttar Pradesh

Profile _____

Highly motivated and skilled content writer with approximately two years of experience in creating high-quality, engaging content for various media platforms. As a final-year graduate in English Literature with a passion for writing, I am eager to gain more practical experience in the field of content writing. I'm always keen on learning new skills. Communication skills, fast learning, and, leadership skills are some of my strengths.

Experience _____

Betterhalf Remote

Content Writer Intern

April 2023 - PRESENT

Handled content writing for the matrimonial Website, writing about-venues, decoration businesses, astronomy, blogs, and other matrimonial
articles.

Saman Technosys Remote

CONTENT WRITER INTERN October 2022 - March 2023

• I was responsible for handling content writing for websites, blogs, brochures, etc.

DigiMarketish Remote

Content Writer Intern August 2021 - February 2022

Primary responsibility was to write News articles. Gained hands-on experience in using WordPress. I also worked on writing content for websites, blogs, and articles.

Skills

WRITING:

Content Writing, Proofreading, Research & facts checking, Editing for Style, Blog Writing, Creative Writing,
 Social Media Marketing.

TECHNICAL:

• Search Engine Optimization (SEO), WordPress, Canva, MS Office.

Education _____

Indira Gandhi National Open University

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN ENGLISH LITERATURE

ST. JOSEPH'S GIRLS INTER COLLEGE

CLASS XII

SENIOR SECONDARY

ST. FRANCIS' CONVENT SCHOOL

Agra, UP

Pursuing

Agra, UP

Agra, UP

2017